♪
( Kirito yells )
GOD DAMN IT.
HOW COULD YOU LET YOURSELF
GIVE IN TO THE SYNTHESIS RITUAL?
YOU FORGET
WHY YOU’RE A SWORDSMAN,
WHY YOU LEFT RULID AND CAME
TO CENTORIA IN THE FIRST PLACE?
YOU’RE HERE FOR ALICE.
YOU’RE HERE TO TAKE HER
BACK HOME WITH YOU!
( both yell )
( singing in Japanese )
♪
♪ PROUD OF MYSELF ♪
Kirito: EUGEO, YOU AND ME NEVER
HAD A FULL-ON FIGHT BEFORE.
( grunts )
I USED TO THINK ABOUT WHO’D WIN,
THE DAY EVER CAME
WE GOT TO CROSS SWORDS FOR REAL.
TO TELL THE TRUTH,
I KNEW YOU’D BEAT ME ONE DAY,
BUT THAT AIN’T TODAY.
( chuckles )
I’LL SHOW HIM A MOVE
HE’S NEVER SEEN ME DO BEFORE!
( gasps )
Eugeo: BURST ELEMENT.
♪
( Kirito yelps )
( Alice gasps )
HE IS MUCH TOO POWERFUL.
I DOUBT THIS ONE
IS REALLY YOUR FRIEND.
Kirito: WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
IF HE’S BEEN SYNTHESIZED,
WOULDN’T THAT
MAKE HIM SUPER STRONG?
Alice: THAT IS TRUE. HOWEVER...
SOMETHING IS OFF ABOUT HIM.
FOR ONE WHO ONLY JUST BECAME
AN INTEGRITY KNIGHT,
HE SEEMS
TOO ACCUSTOMED TO BATTLE.
INCARNATE ARMS AND THAT AERIAL
ELEMENT SKILL HE JUST USED
ARE FAR TOO ADVANCED
FOR A NEWCOMER TO HAVE MASTERED.
YOU SHOULD LET ME HANDLE HIM.
Kirito: MM-MMM. I GOT THIS.
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
WHEN THIS IS OVER,
I’LL GIVE YOU A NAME.
JUST HELP ME GET THROUGH THIS.
( breathes deeply )
EN GARDE, EUGEO!
♪
( groans )
( gasps )
SNAPPY MOVE. IT GOT A NAME?
Eugeo: BALTO STYLE, STORM WAVE.
Kirito: WAIT. BALTO?
AS IN GOLGOROSSO BALTO?
EUGEO, THINK BACK.
DO YOU REMEMBER THE GUY
THAT TAUGHT YOU HOW TO DO THAT?
Eugeo: I DON’T,
AND I DON’T CARE.
THE ONLY PERSON
I NEED TO REMEMBER IS HER.
SHE IS THE REASON
I USE MY SWORD.
I EXIST
TO ELIMINATE HER ENEMIES.
( Kirito growls )
HE’S GOT A CRYSTAL IN HIS HEAD,
JUST LIKE ELDRIE AND ALICE.
Cardinal: ONCE THE PIETY MODULE
IS INSERTED,
IT EFFECTIVELY BLOCKS
THE LINKS TO MEMORIES.
WITH THAT, THE PROSPECTIVE
KNIGHT’S PAST IS SEALED AWAY,
THE RESULT, A KNIGHT
WHO IS LOYAL TO THE CHURCH
AND TO THEIR CREATOR,
THE PONTIFEX.
Kirito: WHAT MEMORIES
ARE BEING BLOCKED?
IF I CAN FIGURE IT OUT
AND REMIND HIM,
HE’LL SNAP OUT OF IT.
NO. IT’LL TAKE MORE THAN WORDS
TO BREAK ADMINISTRATOR’S SPELL.
I’LL POUR MY HEART
INTO MY SWORD.
THAT’LL REACH HIM!
HELL, IT BETTER!
EUGEO!
♪
I’M GONNA FORCE YOU TO REMEMBER
EVERYONE YOU CARED ABOUT!
BACK IN RULID,
THERE’S A GIRL WAITING FOR YOU!
HER NAME’S SELKA!
AT THE SWORDCRAFT ACADEMY,
GOLGOROSSO WAS YOUR MENTOR,
AND LIENA WAS MINE!
AND TIESE AND RONIE!
’MEMBER WHEN WE LAST SAW ’EM?!
COME ON, MAN!
YOU GOTTA REMEMBER
WHY YOU CAME HERE!
IT’S TO TAKE ALICE BACK HOME!
( Eugeo gasping )
Kirito: REMEMBER, DAMN IT!
( yells )
( Eugeo yells )
♪
( young Kirito chuckles )
Kirito: EUGEO.
HUH?
Eugeo: ALICE.
( Kirito gasps )
D-DO YOU REMEMBER HER?
( gasps )
E-EUGEO.
- ( gasps )
- WATCH OUT!
Eugeo: ENHANCE ARMAMENT.
( Alice gasps )
( Kirito gasping )
EUGEO...
WHY?
( footsteps thudding )
( ice cracks )
( Chudelkin laughing )
♪
I TRUST YOU TOOK CARE
OF THOSE DESPICABLE TRAITORS,
NUMBER THIRTY-TWO.
Eugeo: I HAVE THEM BOTH TRAPPED
IN ICE, PRIME SENATOR, SIR.
THEY CAN’T GO ANYWHERE.
Chudelkin: YOU DON’T SAY!
THAT’S ALL WELL AND GOOD,
MY BOY.
BUT YOU DID NOT
FINISH THEM OFF, DID YOU?
Eugeo: NO, PRIME SENATOR.
I DID NOT.
MY ORDERS FROM THE PONTIFEX
WERE TO STOP THE TRAITORS,
NOT TO KILL THEM.
Chudelkin: THAT WON’T DO.
THAT SIMPLY WON’T DO!
AND WHEN YOU SPEAK TO ME,
YOU CALL ME "YOUR EXCELLENCY."
DO NOT FORGET THAT AGAIN,
NUMBER THIRTY-TWO,
BECAUSE IF YOU DO,
I WILL PUNISH YOU
BY TURNING YOU INTO A HORSE.
AND THEN
I SHALL RIDE ON YOUR BACK,
SHOUTING "GIDDY-UP,
LITTLE HORSIE!
GIDDY-UP!" ( laughs )
I’LL FINISH THEM OFF
AND SHOW HER EMINENCE
WHO’S MORE LOYAL.
( laughing )
HAH!
Eugeo: I HAVE RETURNED, MY LADY.
Administrator:
WELCOME BACK, EUGEO.
DID YOU COMPLETE
THE TASK I GAVE YOU?
- Eugeo: YES.
- Administrator: WELL DONE!
YOU DESERVE A REWARD. COME.
CLIMB INTO BED WITH ME.
ALL RIGHT. AS PROMISED, I SHALL
GIVE YOU YOUR HEART’S DESIRE...
LOVE FOR YOU AND YOU ALONE.
Eugeo: YES.
Administrator: FIRST, I SHOULD
DO SOMETHING ABOUT THAT WOUND.
NOW, THEN...
LET ME HAVE A LOOK
AT YOUR FACE AGAIN.
I FOUND AN ODD GAP
IN YOUR MEMORY,
AND THAT IS
WHERE I PUT THE MODULE.
CONVENIENT, BUT I SHOULD
NOT HAVE RUSHED THE PROCESS.
I’LL RESYNTHESIZE YOU
PROPERLY.
AND THEN, AFTER THAT,
YOU SHALL HAVE YOUR REWARD.
( Eugeo gasps )
♪
( music playing only )
( gasping )
Administrator:
BE A GOOD BOY, AND STAY STILL.
THIS MODULE IS A VAST
IMPROVEMENT OVER THE OLD ONES.
IT BOLSTERS THE IMAGINATION
AND UNLOCKS ADVANCED ARTS
LIKE INCARNATE ARMS.
NOW RELAX, AND SHOW ME
YOUR MEMORIES AGAIN,
AND, THIS TIME, I’LL INSERT IT
INTO THE MEMORY
YOU HOLD MOST DEAR.
YOU CAN’T MOVE,
BUT YOU MAY SPEAK.
NOW CHANT THE SPELL
I TAUGHT YOU. GO ON.
DON’T TELL ME
YOU’VE FORGOTTEN IT ALREADY.
OH, YOU SILLY THING.
"REMOVE CORE PROTECTION."
( Eugeo gasping )
( Administrator chuckles )
( sighs )
( gasps )
( Eugeo grunting ) MO-MO...
MO...( stammering )
MOVE!
Administrator: HOW DARE YOU?!
( Eugeo screams )
( grunting )
( screams )
Administrator: I SEE
YOU REGAINED YOUR SENSES.
I CAN’T BELIEVE YOU FOOLED ME.
I ASSUME THE LITTLE BRAT
FROM THE LIBRARY
GAVE YOU THAT KNIFE, YES?
( chuckles )
STAB ME ALL YOU WANT.
I AM IMPERVIOUS TO IT.
NO METAL OBJECT
CAN PIERCE MY SKIN.
- ( Eugeo gasps )
- YOU POOR CHILD,
TO REJECT THE PROMISE I MADE.
ALL YOU HAD TO DO
WAS GIVE YOURSELF TO ME,
AND I WOULD
LOVE YOU BACK IN RETURN,
THE KIND OF LOVE YOU SOUGHT
ALL YOUR LIFE, ETERNAL LOVE,
ETERNAL CONTROL, AND YOU
CHOSE TO REJECT IT LIKE THIS.
Eugeo: ETERNAL LOVE?
ETERNAL CONTROL.
Administrator:
THAT’S RIGHT, EUGEO.
IF YOU GIVE YOURSELF TO ME,
THAT THIRST
YOU’VE BEEN SUFFERING FROM
WOULD BE INSTANTLY QUENCHED,
AND ALL THE CONFUSION AND FEAR
YOU HARBORED FOR SO LONG
WOULD DISAPPEAR.
BUT I SHALL GIVE YOU
ONE MORE CHANCE.
TAKE YOUR SWORD,
AND SMASH THAT TOY.
DO THAT, AND I SHALL
FORGIVE YOUR SINS
AND SHOWER YOU WITH
THE BOUNTY OF MY LOVE.
Eugeo: TO LOVE IS TO CONTROL
AND TO BE CONTROLLED.
IF THAT IS HOW YOU THINK OF IT,
THEN I FEEL SORRY FOR YOU.
( Administrator chuckles )
Eugeo: MAYBE THAT’S
HOW YOU FEEL,
STARVED FOR LOVE,
LOOKING ALL OVER,
AND NEVER FINDING IT.
BUT LOVE ISN’T ABOUT CONTROL,
AND YOU DON’T GIVE IT TO GET
SOMETHING, LIKE A TRANSACTION.
YOU GIVE IT SELFLESSLY,
LIKE YOU GIVE WATER TO A FLOWER.
THAT’S LOVE,
REAL, HONEST LOVE.
Administrator: WHAT A SHAME.
I WANTED TO FORGIVE YOU
FOR YOUR TREASONOUS ACTS
AGAINST THE CHURCH.
I WANTED TO SAVE YOUR SOUL,
AND THIS IS
HOW YOU SPEAK TO ME.
♪
( Eugeo gasping )
Administrator:
I COULD DRAIN YOUR LIFE
AND TURN YOU INTO A JEWEL
IF I WANTED,
BUT THAT WOULD BE A WASTE.
INSTEAD, I’LL SYNTHESIZE YOU
BY FORCE, LIKE HER.
Eugeo: YOU MEAN...
Administrator: THAT’S RIGHT,
SWEET NUMBER THIRTY,
THE ONE YOU’RE
SO INFATUATED WITH.
SHE ALSO REFUSED
TO CHANT THE SPELL,
AND IT TOOK
THE AUTOMATED SENATORS DAYS
TO DISABLE HER CORE PROTECTION.
Eugeo: YOU MONSTERS!
Administrator:
I DIDN’T ACTUALLY SEE IT.
I WAS ASLEEP.
I’M SURE
IT WAS AGONIZING FOR HER.
( Eugeo growls )
Administrator: OH, WELL.
IN THE END,
YOU, TOO, WILL SUFFER
THE SAME EXPERIENCE.
( Eugeo yelling )
♪
I WILL BREAK THROUGH!
( yelling )
( Administrator gasps )
( groans )
( sword clatters )
Administrator: HUMPH!
( Eugeo grunting )
Administrator: THAT SWORD.
OH, NOW I SEE.
( Chudelkin whimpering )
SAVE ME!
( gasps )
OH, PLEASE, YOUR EMINENCE!
I NEED ASSISTANCE HERE!
( gasps ) YOU TRAITOR!
THIS LITTLE BASTARD
BETRAYED YOU, YOUR EMINENCE!
HE SAID HE TRAPPED NUMBER THIRTY
AND THAT OTHER ROGUE,
BUT HE DIDN’T EVEN--
( screams )
LET GO! LET GO!
( whimpering )
♪
Eugeo: KIRITO.
( chuckles )
Kirito: WHAT’S UP, EUGEO?
( laughs )
( Eugeo chuckles )
( crying )
SORRY.
I GAVE IN
TO ADMINISTRATOR’S TEMPTATION
AND TRIED TO KILL YOU BOTH.
I WANTED TO SACRIFICE MYSELF
TO ATONE FOR IT.
Kirito: I KNEW THAT’S
WHAT YOU WERE GOIN’ FOR.
WE BEEN FRIENDS SO LONG,
I CAN READ YOU LIKE A BOOK.
( Eugeo gasps )
( chuckles )
YOU NEVER CHANGE, DO YOU?
( Kirito chuckles )
( Eugeo gasps )
ALICE...
( sniffles )
( Kirito chuckles )
IS THAT HER, ADMINISTRATOR?
Alice: YES. SHE LOOKS THE SAME
AS SHE DID SIX YEARS AGO.
Administrator:
BERCOULI AND FANATIO
WERE JUST ABOUT DUE
FOR ME TO RESET THEM,
BUT YOU, ALICE,
I’VE ONLY HAD YOU
FOR, WHAT, SIX YEARS NOW?
YOUR LOGIC CIRCUITS
DON’T SEEM TO BE MALFUNCTIONING.
PERHAPS THAT IRREGULAR UNIT
IS INFLUENCING YOU. HMM.
( Alice grunts )
Administrator:
WHAT IS IT, ALICE?
IF YOU WISH TO SAY SOMETHING
TO ME, THEN JUST SAY IT.
I WON’T GET MAD.
PLEASE, SPEAK YOUR MIND.
( Alice gasps )
( sighs )
♪
I WILL, YOUR EMINENCE.
AS OF TODAY, THE PROUD ORDER
OF THE INTEGRITY KNIGHTS
HAS FALLEN.
( Administrator sighs )
Alice: ALL IT TOOK
TO BRING IT DOWN
WERE THE SWORDS
OF THE TWO REBELS AT MY SIDE
AND THE OBSESSION
AND DECEIT OF YOUR RULE,
REPRESENTED BY THIS CATHEDRAL!
MY DUTY IS
NOT TO PROTECT THE CHURCH,
BUT TO PROTECT THE INNOCENT
AND SAFEGUARD THEIR PEACE.
IT IS YOUR ACTIONS,
MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE,
WHICH THREATEN THE WELL-BEING
OF THE CITIZENS
OF THE HUMAN EMPIRE.
( Administrator chuckles )
Chudelkin: YOU, SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
HOW DARE--
DUTY, YOU SAY,
YOU BROKEN TOY?!
HAH! YOU KNIGHTS ARE
NOTHING MORE THAN DOLLS.
YOUR "DUTY," AS YOU PUT IT,
IS TO DO WHAT I...
Administrator: FASCINATING.
IT ISN’T A LOGIC CIRCUIT ERROR
AFTER ALL,
AND HER PIETY MODULE
IS STILL FUNCTIONING,
WHICH MEANS
SHE MUST HAVE DISABLED
THE CODE 871
THAT WAS INSTALLED FOR ME
BY HER OWN VOLITION,
RATHER THAN BY SUDDEN EMOTION.
Kirito: THAT THING IN HER EYE’S
CALLED CODE 871?
Administrator: I WON’T
KNOW HOW IT HAPPENED
UNTIL I RUN AN ANALYSIS.
- NOW, THEN, CHUDELKIN...
- ( Chudelkin gasps )
Administrator:
SINCE I AM GENEROUS,
I SHALL GIVE YOU THE CHANCE
TO RESTORE
YOUR TATTERED REPUTATION.
USE YOUR SACRED ARTS,
AND DEAL WITH THOSE THREE.
Chudelkin:
B-B-BUT, YOUR EMINENCE!
YOUR GLORIOUSNESS!
Administrator: YES? WHAT IS IT?
- ( Chudelkin whimpers )
- ( all gasp )
Chudelkin:
FOR THE FIRST AND ONLY TIME
IN MY MANY YEARS
OF SERVICE TO YOU,
I WOULD LIKE TO PRESENT YOU
WITH A MOST IMPUDENT REQUEST.
I SHALL HAPPILY RISK MY LIFE
ANNIHILATING THESE TRAITORS.
HOWEVER...
ONCE I HAVE FULFILLED
YOUR WISHES, WOULD YOU--
( stammers ) W-WOULD YOU
LET ME TOUCH YOUR EXALTED BODY
AND K-K-KISS YOUR LIPS
AND SP-SP-SPEND ONE
MAGICAL NIGHT ALONE WITH YOU?!
UH, PLEASE!
PLEASE!
I WOULD BE MOST GRATEFUL
IF YOU GRANTED ME
SUCH A DELIGHT!
( Administrator laughs )
VERY WELL, CHUDELKIN.
( Chudelkin gasps )
Administrator: I SWEAR
TO THE GODDESS STACIA,
AS SOON AS YOU
HAVE FULFILLED YOUR MISSION,
MY BODY WILL BE YOURS
FOR THE TAKING,
EVERY INCH, FOR ONE NIGHT.
( Chudelkin gasps )
WORDS CANNOT EXPRESS
THE JOY YOU’VE BROUGHT ME,
YOUR EXALTED HOLINESS!
AND I SWEAR TO YOU,
I WILL NOT LET YOU DOWN.
HUP!
I AM RESOLUTE AND ENERGIZED!
I AM MOTIVATED,
AND I AM INVINCIBLE!
SYSTEM CALL!
GENERATE THERMAL ELEMENT!
( groans )
- ( Kirito gasps )
- ( Chudelkin chuckles )
NOW I WILL SHOW YOU
MY GREATEST SACRED ART!
COME FORTH, GENIE,
AND BURN THESE TRAITORS TO ASH!
( all gasp )
♪
Singer: ♪ OH, EVERYTHING
TURNS TO ASH, TO ASH ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ AND EVERYTHING
TURNS TO DUST, TO DUST ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ FORGET-ME-NOT ♪